

Bruno Sá Marques

Graphic Designer

CONTACT

Email

samarques.bruno@gmail.com

Phone

+351 933221136

Profile

I worked with many high-profile clients, national and multinational contractors to support execution of major engineering projects in the Oil and Gas industry.

Reliable, self motivated individual who performs under pressure and enjoys working in a challenging and demanding environment.

I'm punctual, well organised with a positive attitude to change and experience of managing others.

Highly creative, with some experience in editing video and sound.

Music compositions, videos, photography, drawings and poetry available in my online Portfolio.

Experience

DOCUMENT SPECIALIST / 2002 - 2012 (LONDON UK)

KBR, Inc. 2011 - 2012

M.W. Kellogg Limited 2002 - 2011

Supervising Tech Clerk activities.

Updating and Issuing Engineering & Vendor documents using IPMS. Database creation on Access and Excel and cover design on Photoshop for CD handover to the client.

Documentum management (Webtop).

Education

• COURSE MULTIMEDIA SPECIALIST / 2020 - 2021

Currently being trained by CINEL towards a Level 5 Multimedia Specialist Certification.

• COURSE PV INSTALLER / 2017 - 2018

Level 4 Professional Certificate by CINEL.

. OPEN UNIVERSITY UK / 2010 - 2012

Certificate of Higher Education (Creative Writing)

. ARCO SCHOOL OF ARTS / 96 - 97

Skills

Photoshop	••••••
After Effects	•••••
Audition	•••••
Illustrator	
Premiere	
HTML	••••00000
CSS	•••000000
JavaScript	••0000000
Maya 3D	••••00000

Languages

ENG •••••• 100% **PT** •••••• 100%